# **Eric Corona**

209.200.5406 | ericcorona3@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/e-corona/ |  $\Omega$  ericcorona1

## **SUMMARY**

As a Front-End Web Developer with experience in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, I'm passionate about making a positive impact in my community. With crisis management and resource management skills, I can make a valuable contribution to your projects.

# **EDUCATION**

#### **freeCodeCamp**

• Responsive Web Development & Javascript Algorithms

#### William Jessup University, Rocklin, CA

• Graduated 2018 with a Bachelor of Arts in Youth Ministry

### **EXPERIENCE**

Transformative Education Counselor My Friend's Place, Los Angeles, CA | 2019-Present

- Developed proficiency in Google Apps Script to automate and integrate data tracking, email, and calendar functionalities, resulting in improved accuracy and streamlined communication processes.
- Strengthened Spanish language proficiency to facilitate engagement with Spanish-only speakers within the department, enhancing cross-team collaboration and communication.
- Collaborated with diverse teams and clients to identify and create actionable goals, establish clear expectations, and develop effective strategies to achieve desired outcomes. Program Director

### One-Eighty Youth Programs, Lodi, CA | 2017-2019

- Updated website and social media, stabilized posting schedule, and increased engagement and following by 100%.
- Created a comfortable, safe, and fun atmosphere uniquely suitable for reaching varying demographics within the surrounding community, resulting in a 25% increase in program enrollment and retention.
- Built relationships with parents, youth, and schools to identify patterns, encourage growth, and provide resources, resulting in 90% positive feedback from program participants and stakeholders.

#### Youth Director Cornerstone Church of Lodi, Lodi, CA | 2014-2017

- Established relationships with students and parents in order to encourage, guide, and develop their daily spiritual growth, resulting in 75% increase in attendance and engagement.
- Facilitated events and meetings in order to follow the vision of the church and to meet the needs of the students and families, resulting in a 90% satisfaction rate from program participants.
- Developed a small team of leaders focused on supporting the students and parents, resulting in a 300% increase in volunteer participation and retention.